### ANANDA APRILIANI PRATIWI

# Web Developer

089697269723 | anandapratiwi426@gmail.com | Cibabat, Kota Cimahi, Jawa Barat https://www.linkedin.com/in/ananda-apriliani-pratiwi/ | https://honanda123.github.io/anandaaprilianip/

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am a graduate of the Bachelor Informatics Engineering at the Universitas Komputer Indonesia (UNIKOM). I am a person who can work in a team as a member or a leader, I really like to learn new things, have a strong determination to achieve something. Have expertise in programming such as web programming and android programming.

#### **EDUCATION**

**Universitas Komputer Indonesia** 2018 – 2022

Informatics Engineering Study Program GDA 3.62/4.00

**SMA Negeri 3 Cimahi** 2015 – 2018

Jurusan MIPA

### ORGANIZATIONAL EXPERIENCE

Unikom Robotics Division 2018-2022

Member

- Maintenance and development of robots in the division

**English Club** 2016-2018

Member

- Laison Officer of City Level English Debate Competition 2016

## **CERTIFICATION**

Web Development - Junior Web Developer

Oracle Academy - Database Programming with SQL

### WORK EXPERIENCE

Kantor Kesatuan Bangsa dan Politik

August 2021 - September 2021

Internship

- Create a Company Profile Website for Kesbang
- Manage incoming and outgoing mail
- Make internship letters, and research letters

### TASKS AND PROJECTS

## **Block Based Robotic Learning Application**

March 2022 – August 2022

Android developer

- Implementing block programming on android applications as a robotic learning medium for elementary school children

## **Company Profile Website Kesbangpol Cimahi**

August 2021 – September 2021

Web developer

- Built to make it easier for the public to get various information about Kesbangpol Kota Cimahi

## Diet-in Aja Website

November 2020 – January 2021

Web Developer

- Built to inform as well as help with dieting

## Diet-in Aja Apps

Mei 2021 – Agustus 2021

Android Developer

- Developing the Diet-in Aja website into an android application

### **EXPERTISE AND SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- Bootsrap
- PHP
- Codeigniter
- Java
- Figma
- Microsoft office

- Leadership
- Problem-Solving
- Teamwork
- Time management
- Discipline